[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2008-02-10 13:20:53
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: ED,ms gothic,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,2,0,0,30,1
Style: OP,ms gothic,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,3,8,0,0,10,1
Style: SP,Microsoft YaHei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,30,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.13,0:01:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.33,0:02:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,古時在中國北部流傳著這樣一個神話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.93,0:02:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位皇子解放了被龍族壓迫的人類的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.05,0:02:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她憑藉大地之神的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.45,0:02:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消滅了龍族
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.12,0:02:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將大地還給了人們
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.36,0:02:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位神明就是安泰神,或叫做冥界神
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.99,0:02:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相當於日本神話中的素盞明尊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.57,0:02:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這場戰爭中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.37,0:02:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渾身沾滿了龍族戰士之血的皇子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.10,0:02:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到了不老不死之身
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.81,0:02:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了後世
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.54,0:03:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的故事就變成八百比丘尼的神話故事的起源
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.85,0:03:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大地之神和皇子聯手給予後人和平安詳的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.95,0:03:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並約定未來永恆的繁榮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.39,0:03:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.37,0:04:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上,一頭巨大的龍出現\N並襲擊這個山下祥和小鎮,造成大的傷亡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.24,0:04:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且一夜之間這裏的湖水全幹了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.17,0:04:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是超出人類想像的靈異現象
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.51,0:04:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍突然從湖中出現
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.41,0:04:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所引起的波濤損壞了沿岸居民的住房
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.48,0:04:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大量民居被龍所吐出的火焰所燒盡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.42,0:04:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緊跟著巨龍出現的,並將其打倒隨即閃光消失的巨人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.36,0:04:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在有關專家正在調查他的真身
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.23,0:04:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個小鎮在半個月前
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.57,0:04:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就連續發生了謎樣殺人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.63,0:04:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人認為這次的事件與其有關
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.04,0:04:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到目前為止事情仍毫無進展
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.42,0:04:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.19,0:04:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五郎!五郎!振作一點!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.99,0:05:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油!堅持住!五郎!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.26,0:05:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你們,誰來救救我的孩子!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.50,0:05:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你們!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.67,0:05:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你們!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.37,0:05:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我的孩子!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.99,0:05:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情況怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.18,0:05:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.33,0:05:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.00,0:05:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我…害大家變成這樣的!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.40,0:05:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.64,0:05:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.14,0:05:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不是這樣的!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.21,0:05:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個現在打算到哪里去?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.58,0:05:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要跟我一起走
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.94,0:06:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天龍!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.24,0:06:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天龍!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.23,0:07:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你總算回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.36,0:07:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僧正大人,好久不見
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.78,0:08:08.72,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かごめ,かごめ,かごめ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.88,0:08:13.22,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かごのなかのとりは
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:17.69,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いついつでやう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.21,0:08:21.64,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よあけのばんに
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.15,0:08:25.97,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つるとかめとすべった
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.99,0:08:29.77,OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うしろのしょうめんだあれ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.78,0:08:08.72,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠女 籠女 籠女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.88,0:08:13.22,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠中的鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.29,0:08:17.69,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無時無刻地想要出來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.21,0:08:21.64,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在黎明的黑夜裏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.15,0:08:25.97,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白鶴與烏龜滑一跤的時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.99,0:08:29.77,SP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背後的那個是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.99,0:08:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(代表著壽命的白鶴與龜滑了一跤象徵是死產)
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.16,0:08:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可愛吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.83,0:08:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這附近孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.83,0:08:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們常常到這裏來玩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.00,0:08:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱砂晃一不願意來這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.77,0:08:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也沒有辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.87,0:08:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每個人都有自己的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.68,0:08:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能既希望於沒有人都順從我們
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.41,0:08:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我們已經沒有時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.62,0:08:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能就這樣放著不管
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.59,0:08:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為天龍就要來了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.12,0:08:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有結界都是由那個來保持平衡的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.63,0:08:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果松浦家的預言沒有錯的話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.67,0:08:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.53,0:09:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在中國地區有低氣壓形成
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.37,0:09:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在向東部移動
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.11,0:09:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關西地區今晚將持續降雨天氣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關東地區明日下午五時也會降雨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.01,0:09:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外沿海地區的波浪很大
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.35,0:09:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請船隻多加注意
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.62,0:09:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在搞什麼鬼!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.69,0:09:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.42,0:09:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這附近可有很奇怪的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.59,0:10:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們先回山裏去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.67,0:10:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.30,0:10:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想像我們喝酒鬧事還早了十年?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.38,0:10:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點回家喝奶睡覺去吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.29,0:10:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.59,0:10:30.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛才還在想要放過你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.13,0:10:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是不知好歹!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.61,0:10:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.18,0:10:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後打架要先看准物件才下手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.61,0:10:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.65,0:10:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們再找一家繼續喝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.55,0:11:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.89,0:11:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.69,0:11:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以站起來嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.76,0:11:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別碰我!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不要管我的事!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.81,0:11:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.95,0:11:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是我真正的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.32,0:11:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是我真正…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.49,0:11:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的力量!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.33,0:11:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此,我知道為什麼小夜子沒說服他了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.01,0:11:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扇一郎\N籠女 籠女
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.35,0:12:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠中的鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.69,0:12:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無時無刻地想要出來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.06,0:12:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子和我一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.80,0:12:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你還留在這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.80,0:12:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會讓你的身體折磨到死為止
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.83,0:12:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都是單身一人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.30,0:12:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有任何的後顧之憂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.77,0:12:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧,小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.82,0:12:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.85,0:12:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我站住!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.02,0:12:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在哪里!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.99,0:12:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那裏!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.59,0:12:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.84,0:12:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子,你沒事吧,小夜子?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.17,0:13:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來你們在這裏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.75,0:13:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扇一郎!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.43,0:13:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扇一郎!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.94,0:13:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.08,0:14:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慈雲坊現在回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.12,0:14:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回來了,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.12,0:14:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.03,0:14:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們的能力不足
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.83,0:14:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟丟了天龍的行蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.53,0:14:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是沒有辦法的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.54,0:14:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也累了吧,去休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.34,0:14:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.81,0:14:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.48,0:14:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把在街上鬧事的朱砂晃一帶回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.18,0:14:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.05,0:14:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先行告退了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.45,0:16:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜靜地坐好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.42,0:16:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我的腿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.36,0:16:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你是一樣這樣坐著
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.73,0:16:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我辦得到的話,你也一樣能行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.73,0:16:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.37,0:16:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不像小夜子那樣!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.90,0:16:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我無法做到你那樣!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.51,0:16:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論能否做到都不應該說這種話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.24,0:16:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須要學會忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.88,0:16:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你容易受到各種雜念的影響
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.25,0:16:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才會招來像上次那樣的災禍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.49,0:16:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須要自律
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.22,0:16:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的體質容易招來強大的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.83,0:16:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能以自身的意識來控制它的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.26,0:16:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你一定能夠超越我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.43,0:16:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那就是你的命運的話,你也只能直面它,超越它
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.91,0:16:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不行的!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.77,0:16:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能成為像你那樣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.48,0:17:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.39,0:17:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一 晃一
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.06,0:17:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾乃根之國的武神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.16,0:17:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾欲借你的身體和龍來戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.03,0:17:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一,龍即將禍及大地,接受吾的意識吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.97,0:17:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.82,0:17:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.56,0:17:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人嗎!快把我放出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.26,0:17:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!快把我放出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.36,0:17:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人嗎!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.00,0:17:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.57,0:17:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別管他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.40,0:18:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠女 籠女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.37,0:18:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠中的鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.11,0:18:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無時無刻地想要出來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.15,0:18:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在黎明的黑夜裏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.02,0:18:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白鶴與烏龜滑滑一跤的時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.56,0:18:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣,習慣這裏的生活了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.69,0:18:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.46,0:18:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然很辛苦,但是要努力啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.59,0:18:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不僅是為了你好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.06,0:18:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是你對所死去的人所唯一能做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.57,0:18:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.27,0:18:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠女 籠女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.24,0:18:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠中的鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.71,0:18:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那首歌嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.68,0:18:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是籠子歌嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.78,0:18:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是首關於日本妓院的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.79,0:18:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠女就是籠中的妓女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.36,0:18:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被男人購買一夜玩弄的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.66,0:18:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化為歌中的鳥兒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.63,0:19:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人是鶴,男人是龜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.93,0:19:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和心愛的男人一起逃出妓院的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.54,0:19:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你不會相信
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.81,0:19:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200年前,小夜子是個妓女
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.41,0:19:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.08,0:19:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這大概就是松浦家的罪孽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.62,0:19:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己所背負的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.32,0:19:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在罪孽消失前是無法死去的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.43,0:19:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿姨!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.73,0:19:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我們一起玩吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.16,0:19:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.53,0:19:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她準備用自己的一身來償還松浦家所犯下的罪孽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.37,0:19:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他在明治初年就來到本寺了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.37,0:19:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松浦家的罪孽?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.07,0:19:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是為了消滅龍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.91,0:19:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.01,0:19:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去!放我出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.25,0:19:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有在!可惡!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.39,0:19:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放我出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.09,0:19:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.86,0:20:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好焦躁的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.46,0:20:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一也在這裏嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.20,0:20:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不,聽說他昨晚喝酒鬧事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.37,0:20:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待會你拿晚飯給他
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.14,0:20:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照美?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.31,0:20:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.75,0:20:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都想要來利用我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.35,0:21:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了,隨便他們去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.56,0:21:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.10,0:21:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得這裏的生活怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.60,0:21:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你過的也真辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.44,0:21:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走投無路只能到這裏來當下人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.61,0:21:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實,小夜子她教了我很多東西
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.75,0:21:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像這個叫做九字真言
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.75,0:21:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我還沒有像小夜子那樣熟練,但是我每天…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.79,0:21:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再說了!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.96,0:21:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再說了!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.56,0:21:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你學那種東西有什麼用?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.63,0:21:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遇到危險的話,我會保護你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.84,0:21:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很簡單,只要我繼續當我的怪物就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.01,0:21:54.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.31,0:21:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我能做些什麼的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.28,0:21:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別傻了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.48,0:22:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是那些和尚利用的道具而已!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.51,0:22:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣的,晃一
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.55,0:22:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子和其他人都是真的在擔心我們
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.19,0:22:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就把我抓到這裏來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.66,0:22:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓來這裏?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.67,0:22:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.33,0:22:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你喜歡好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.40,0:22:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你喜歡去學那些騙人的法術
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.04,0:22:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再去求龍,請它再把你變得漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.36,0:22:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…為什麼你要說這麼過分的話
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.03,0:22:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易才見到你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.13,0:22:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不奢望你能夠喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.00,0:22:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.07,0:23:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.17,0:23:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滾出去!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.89,0:23:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真是個沒有的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.19,0:23:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是在怕什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.63,0:23:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你抓我來這裏是幹什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.80,0:23:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天龍現在開始行動尋找武神
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.87,0:23:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要是你被殺死了,我們就會很困擾
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.41,0:23:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有龍在?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.65,0:23:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天地兩界的結界被打破了,它們就都逃出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.65,0:23:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開玩笑?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.65,0:23:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不幹了!我可不想再和怪物戰鬥了!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.02,0:23:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.99,0:23:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經接受了武神的意識
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.93,0:23:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在說什麼都是無用的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.43,0:24:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是我自願的?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.70,0:24:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要讓我碰上這種倒楣的事情!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.94,0:24:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情應該跟我沒有任何關係!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.71,0:24:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有任何關係!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.64,0:24:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有完沒完!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.48,0:24:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼和你沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.31,0:24:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍的目標就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.62,0:24:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你體內的武神
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.65,0:24:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點清醒些吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.79,0:24:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃避現實是沒有任何用的!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.73,0:24:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借酒澆愁,哭泣是不能解決任何問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.63,0:24:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感到害怕又不是只有你一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.60,0:24:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也是,沒有想要死
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.85,0:24:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子,請告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.29,0:24:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.29,0:24:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"活"是什麼意思?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.89,0:25:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就很難說了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.13,0:25:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請告訴我!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.63,0:25:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在來這裏的途中
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.10,0:25:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好幾次想到要死
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.03,0:25:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本就看不到活著的意義
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.74,0:25:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又醜又內向\N僅僅為自己變漂亮就讓大家受這麼大苦難
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.31,0:25:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的我哪里還有活著的價值
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.35,0:25:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在再想這些東西也沒有什麼用了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.55,0:25:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊,一點都沒有了,我什麼都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.73,0:25:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要還活著就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.26,0:25:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人總有一天會死的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.87,0:25:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到那一天才能決定一個人的價值
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.84,0:25:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人的價值不一樣,每個人都有自己的命運
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.97,0:25:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是面對命運的挑戰,還是去逃避命運
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.41,0:25:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這都會決定人的死法
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.88,0:26:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為人類是為了好的死法才拼命的活下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.09,0:26:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子,我真的能成為像你這樣的人嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.90,0:26:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.23,0:26:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直面自己的弱點的人才能成為強者
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.51,0:26:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天你會超越我的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.24,0:26:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臨 兵 鬥 者 
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.54,0:26:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起風了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.78,0:27:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它終於要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.21,0:27:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起,因為我的任性而拖累了大家
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.12,0:27:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少臭美了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.39,0:27:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是憑我們自己的意識來行動的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.72,0:27:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的行動只靠僧正和小夜子,負擔是不是太重了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.07,0:27:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還在練習
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.30,0:27:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.97,0:27:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才謝謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.88,0:27:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想繼續努力下去
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.11,0:27:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.91,0:27:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我再教你一點
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.65,0:27:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結印的時候,把精神集中在指尖
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.14,0:27:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記住剛才的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.94,0:28:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是一切的基本
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.91,0:28:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才那是…?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.41,0:28:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,氣的相碰,我的和你的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.93,0:28:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想要逃走的話,就從內院走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.07,0:29:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了,你不逃了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.18,0:29:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍馬上就要來這裏了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.68,0:29:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要逃的話就趁現在
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.41,0:29:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不阻止我逃跑嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.25,0:29:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己的人生由你自己來決定怎麼走,我是不會干涉的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.33,0:29:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若你覺得逃的掉的話,那你就逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.26,0:29:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有件事我必須提醒你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.57,0:29:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍在追尋的是你和小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.70,0:29:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦它毀掉了這裏,下一個目標就是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.02,0:29:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就行了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.12,0:29:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可是我看重的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.12,0:29:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定會憑藉自己的意志回來的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.99,0:30:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望慈雲坊他們不要強行把他帶回來
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.53,0:30:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.83,0:30:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經讓他們去守衛金鋼門的各處
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.17,0:30:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再過去則是我守護的冥王門
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.98,0:30:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於到了這個時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.79,0:31:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.29,0:31:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在幹什麼!快點會廂房去!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.13,0:31:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要一起來戰鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.50,0:31:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能幫什麼忙?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.13,0:31:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的你只能成為我們的累贅
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.80,0:31:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快到結界外面去
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.97,0:31:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.64,0:31:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看著我們戰鬥到最後吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.31,0:31:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臨 兵 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.18,0:31:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬥 者
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.29,0:31:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆 陣
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.42,0:31:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,列 在
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.82,0:31:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 前
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.83,0:31:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 前
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.30,0:31:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天龍!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.74,0:31:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在幹什麼,快點離開!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.51,0:31:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.77,0:32:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咒語
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.11,0:32:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.48,0:32:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在幹什麼,我不是叫你快點離開!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.92,0:32:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.25,0:32:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.86,0:32:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種程度的傷想死也死不了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.20,0:32:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結界快要消失了!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.30,0:32:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.71,0:33:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.97,0:33:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼事了?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.30,0:33:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的氣比龍的電擊更強
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.01,0:33:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的氣?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.44,0:33:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了,剩下的就是我的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.28,0:33:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快點走吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.52,0:33:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心庵!坊庵!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.83,0:33:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然靠我們是封印不住它的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.87,0:34:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.15,0:34:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.09,0:34:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僧正!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.46,0:34:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子,請給我力量吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.60,0:34:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是只有你一個人感到害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.64,0:34:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都還不想去死
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.71,0:34:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.45,0:34:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若你覺得逃的掉的話,那你就逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.64,0:35:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武神!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.47,0:35:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.55,0:37:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到業雲之劍會被折斷
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.35,0:37:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武神!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.10,0:37:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.77,0:37:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然還是回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.32,0:37:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.17,0:38:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武神!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.31,0:39:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晃一
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.98,0:39:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.09,0:39:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子!振作點!小夜子!快睜開眼睛啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.39,0:39:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再哭了,照美
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.00,0:39:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.11,0:39:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扇一郎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.51,0:39:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼!我不要這樣!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.85,0:39:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還有跟你學很多事情!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.72,0:39:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼可以就這樣死去了!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.82,0:40:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太過分了,小夜子!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.68,0:40:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼!為什麼!晃一的內心呐喊著!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.22,0:40:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不見自己所應該走的道路!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.62,0:40:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱砂晃一十七歲之冬就這樣結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.83,0:40:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,籠女 籠女  籠中的鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.24,0:40:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無時無刻地想要出來 
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.04,0:40:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在黎明的黑夜裏
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.01,0:40:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白鶴與烏龜滑滑一跤的時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.01,0:41:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背後的那個是誰


